Awesome. Mine says:
"To my friend Howard.
From Stan Lee. Excelsior!"
Mine says, "To Raj. From Stan Lee."
That's because you pissed him off
about his character names.
(Raj:)I didn't even mention
Dum Dum Dugan...
(Raj:)...or Green Goblin, Matt Murdock,
Pepper Potts, Victor von Doom.
(Raj:)Oh, and worst of all, Millie the Model.
(Penny:)We're home.
(Leonard:)-Oh, hey, buddy. How'd it go?
-You know very well how it went.
Yeah. But we all wanna
hear it from you.
(Sheldon:)-I was found guilty and fined $533.
-I'm gonna write you a check for that.
(Penny:)As long as you promise to put it in your
drawer and never cash it like the others.
(Sheldon:)I also now have three points on
a driver's license I do not yet possess...